oh
for the netherlands and not per previously uncapped
of course has performed like a tournament
veteran jury
and timber withstands the challenge of mattis
to licked in an unchanged back three
the two wing backs
splint and dumb fries both scored against the usa between them
frankie de jong wins his fiftieth cap
and steven bergvn replaces david carson in the attacking department
with cody who scored in the first three games
and memphis depay i who scored in the fourth
by this point blank save in the final seconds against australia
which carried argentina through to here
ahead of him is sandra martinez makes a third center back
that is how they finished the last game
actually so beyond the unchanged midfield
there is no starting place for pau gomez
nor and maria lionel messi twenty fourth world cup appearance matches
mislav closer now only lota matus has played more
it's a glimpse sidesteps
a player or two went off with the shot
unusually for him
burst into life
though within range
martin derome and the pie
put it wide
i think memphis dubai wanted to take over here
and they're kind of getting in each other's way
berwhite has it
and to paul with a shot that lacked
vi
i almost think the callis thought this was messy
just coming on to the ball
because there's a chance for mcallister to have a go
himself
memphis to pi
okay by mandy here once again is molina
drafbe taken by messi
wriggling away from mackay
i'm fiddling through a beautiful pass
it's a wonderful argentina goal
molina
poun
messi cut them in half
and the rest was simple
the elbe celeste shine
well it's one of the passes of the world cup
so far it's a magic man
mei
you just don't think he's got anything to go out here
and where's the gap there
it is
it's a beauty and molina
does not disappoint
he's made so many raids down that line side
this time he cuts in it may be a tactic that surprised the netherlands
scored some goals
but this is a genius of an assist from lionel messi
a game that didn't offer too many threats and either
and all of a sudden
messi comes alive
as he has done on a few occasions in this world cup
look at the twist of messi got a shot away
when not many would no expecting him almost to stay on his left foot
but
he just loses
he didn't lose
okay
and he needs not even half a yard to get that shot
by depaul
messi or beautifully weighted mcallister
alvarez is one way to paul is the other
this is rodrigo de paul for argentina alexis
mcallister too much on it
yeah
not bad
just chuck
who now sees a flag that his face suggests he would prefer to have seen earlier
but here's mcallister
a kunya still writhing tom fries glaring
well he catches him
i don't think the gonna
uh
change the best mind there
certainly in the box
with the footwork from the wing back
well the spanish referee is drowning in orange there he
finger to his ear
acknowledging that vr has a say
not quite immaculate from the spots
not even immaculate from the spot at this tournament
but there is no other credible candidate when there is him
frankie dion just telling his keeper with
unless he's gonna put it
reach is out for more history as argentina reach out for the world cup semi finals
he has a dream to fulfill
they have a dream to fulfill
step by step they draw closer to the ultimate fulfillment
made one scored one
he's been at the center of things yet again
dumfriis getting sucked into the challenge
it was a foul
and who do you want at this kind of moment
when the heat's on
yeah
he's missed one
but never looked likely here
he kind of flat footed
and just no keeper didn't really know what to do
and with the subs
the whole of the argentina bench rushing across a fairly tall over
as do the fans
probably
has been to this point quite a night for argentina's full backs his gao
he has stumbled on the challenge referee
got to the scene of the would be crime pretty quickly
but to found
but as it turned out no crime had been committed
it was a nice pass by memphis depay
but
slung in by burke house out by mandy
the dutch of dog back in
retrievable well that switch to simple
straightforward football
get the ball in the box and get it in early to those two set forwards
that is not an easy header
but horse executes it brilliantly
to give his team a sniff of a chance here
this should be some finish to the match
the netherlands have set up here a potential grandstand finish
with their first shot on target in the game
their first attempt on target
and it was an attempt that proved fruitful
a proper orthodox center forwards head up
since when as argentina kicked back off well
he's gone charge against
trying to feed the wide men good quality into the box
van
dyke
gao
thrust up towards the young burhouse
oh
he gave that plenty
fell perfectly onto that powerful left foot of his
still a bit of work to do
though cope minus
down by van dyke
on by ake
chased by gao
and hoisted into the stand
frankie deon seconds to running out up into the air by paredes
oh
that looks like a foul
that is gonna be a free kick
oh
what a silly challenge
what a silly challenge in minutes one hundred
they have had one rehearsal from just about the same spot
well
this could be their last chance
moa on the edge of tears
netherlands on the edge of elimination
one kick of the ball as the ninety ninth minute ticks into the one hundred
and the one hundredth into the one hundred and first messi is in the book
eyes on the prize and the prize is big to stay alive
this is it
code miners
smart
too close
extraordinary
one hundred and one minutes
what a kick that was
and the striker that's done so well since coming on
showed nimble need for work there
what it mattered most
what about this ah
brilliant from the netherlands
brilliant from van horst
and we stare down the barrel of extra time
an equalizer from out
vehorst in borrow time at the end of stoppage time
and they're not going home in which room
so just come on the pitch
hasn't he
there's been plenty of back shot to the ref tonight
paredes for messi
messi to wriggle and messi to shoot high and wide
oh
my god
now toro martinez mona on the dash
dimaria for the first time
fernandez
he's got a yard in by fernandez and crash drive by now
taro martinez
there's a dutch body
in the way there
there was there was a vital dutch body
dimaria drifting away from our camonty al corner
stepped it up
argentina
still waiting for the netherlands to revert to type
with those long balls into the box
given half a chance
and he loops up over and behind
yeah noo was on the ground
have to get up quickly
will he attack this one with some force
headed it with some force
a little shove in the back
making it a bit more difficult
perhaps but argentina look in the side more likely
doing all the pushing at the moment
the dutch skipper gets himself in the way of taro martinez
daintily done by timber
here's luke de jong
chased up by noa lang
it's lags cross
and it's picked off by martinez
with the burke house ghosting in behind
but it didn't he very well to keep up
off his line quickly
number of all the netherlands in second half of extra time argentina done well
team maria on by montel el toro
martinez
pummeled away by nopper
he's got a corner
fifteen seconds to play
perhaps the last act
invite team maria and touched up switchly by noa
that's a cheeky effort from dimaria
i think it's intentional to me
that maybe perhaps the keeper unawares messi
fernandez has hit the post
oh wow
what a pure strike at the football
but no that was nowhere near this
oh
great save
that is a great save from emmy martinez out again
a nation on his shoulders
and messi answers to paul
there's a lovely purity about this man's left boot burke house
oh
another great get by martinez
why wouldn't he dance
for argentina to establish a two goal cushion with three each to take
and argentina are nearly there
and the lights
so if he guesses right
there's every chance he could save it
and the horse does score
has dragged it wide
and the drama for it
to on rolls it in with poise
is the kick of the ball
the tenth penalty of ten
not per doing all that he can in gold to put off his man
a night that has gone on forever
that will be remembered forever
and epic
and then from the spot they want it all over again
it was not his last dance
he will jump and jiji into the semi final
messi is still alive
argentina still alive
the dutch dumbfounded
confounded
and heading home
yeah
and there's not much shaking hands down there
there's plenty of pushing and shoving players having to be separated
me's men have got themselves through
another day of drama at this world cup
too much stuff
but exhausted deal in the days
unbelievable stuff
i mean you can see what it means
it's
it's always horrible for me to watch the
the inside out
it's painful
you know you know what these guys are going through
but i mean they gave it everything
they made it a great game
ultimately martinez with his penalty antics again was was the difference
with the first two penalties
he gave argentina